It means that it's as if there were already a potential that
was about to be born, green.
Do you understand?
It’s the field of form.
So this means that there is not yet,
we say it’s an expression that defines a hypothetical field
that would contain energy without matter.
That’s already a bit more complex.
And this is where it’s going to happen.
We’ve seen the impact down to the core,
tensgrity,
the importance of the matrix here.
We’ve seen all the mechanisms,
that it’s not just an electromagnetic field,
but temperature, heat, mechanical stresses,
hydrostatic pressures, electric fields,
redox systems.
All of this plays into the homeostasis of the system.
The presence of elementary particles
with the notion of electromagnetic energy.
The polarized man, electromagnetic field,
Maxwell's law.
There is the notion of space and time.
There’s even more, there’s light.
We're just going to do this.
I have lots of these lines.
I have a bunch of cells
what makes
them differentiate
we’ve seen that there are changes
and this stress from the cubit
is all about mechanotransduction
I’m putting a lot of light
I’m modifying my parameter
when I have an electric field
what do I have?
I still have an electromagnetic field
and well that allows
the system to have cohesion
But additionally, I have a reference, that means that the cell
that is here, compared to the cell that is here, does not have the
same reference regarding the space in which it is defined.
This means that the heritage that is here will express itself differently
at a given moment compared to the heritage that is here.
Even if initially, all the cells have the same
heritage.
These are layers
that will be able to express
in different spaces and at different times
depending on the chronology
and the place in which
they are relative to the midline
and to the electric field.
Do you understand?
It’s the position that
you have regarding
this electromagnetic field.
Which will release the information.
Among other things.
It’s the CDI.
There are several parameters that come into play
but this is already the first major component
very important
where the polarity comes from
where these forces come from
they were there long before us
they are still here long after us
just
the vibratory concentrated
energy of matter
light induces matter
the fluid, electricity
the fluid and densification
and then at some point, it starts again
and we
We see what makes a cell suddenly become hepatic
and another that will become cerebral.
It’s based on relocation in space and time.
Sometimes, we can take packages of the hymen and place them there.
They can rechange.
Sometimes, they can no longer depending on time.
You now have a good image of the difference between epithelial tissue
and connective tissue.
There could be
the difference between ectoderm, endoderm, mesoderm, so I’m going to give you a
tissue,
I don’t know, something, you’ll just tell me what it is, okay,
the tongue, the
tongue, endoderm, it’s digestive,
I think there will still be a muscle, inside, yes, it's a mix,
of endoderm, epithelial tissue
is endoderm, the muscle tissue is mesoderm.
The pancreas.
But it’s endoderm.
So everything hormonal
comes from epithelial tissue,
from boundary tissue.
This means that all the glands
exocrine, endocrine, etc.
always come
from epithelial tissue. In other words,
they always come from boundary tissue.
In other words, they always derive from ectoderm
or from endoderm.
Never from mesoderm.
That was also important, now that we have the colors.
The base of the skull is a balance
between my neurocranium and my viscerocranium.
I will derive
the tissues. In the first three
weeks,
at the beginning of the third week,
we already have something that has been done.
So we can divide
into three major parts, the period
called embryogenesis,
the period called organogenesis
and the period called the fetal period. In two months,
all the structures,
in two to three months, all my noble structures
will already be formed. After that, it’s
maturation, growth.
I emphasize a lot here, about the notion
of growth, that motility is a movement
that is always present in the body,
and which will be defined by a developmental system.
It’s a movement as we've seen, except it becomes complex in different tissues.
Growth and gametogenesis, we start there.